identifix.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy | Identifix

This privacy statement covers our web site, identifix.com. To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we want to disclose our information practices to you.

Through the registration process and normal course of providing service, Identifix collects information about how our service is used. Identifix also maintains a history of the services provided and a record of each user’s interaction with our website.

We use this information to:

  * Conduct website analysis to help make improvements.
  * Provide a historical reference for our customers.
  * Conduct usage analysis to develop training and marketing efforts.
  * Share information on what fixed the vehicle with other Identifix Direct-Hit subscribers and our customers.

We may share certain elements of user information with our in-house sales reps and our automotive marketing partners. We ask users to provide us with certain information that is needed to complete the billing process and to track usage on Identifix. The required information is clearly indicated on our web site. Services cannot be provided without this information.

Only Identifix employees whose job requires that they access this information (such as our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to sensitive information. In addition, those employees use protected passwords to access our systems, and records are kept of their activities while they are accessing our systems. They log off the systems whenever they leave their work areas.

Customers have the opportunity to correct any inaccurate information and to terminate using our service under the guidelines of our service agreement.

### Information Collection

Identifix is the sole owner of the information collected on identifix.com. Identifix collects information from our customers at several different points on our web site.

### Registration

To register to use identifix.com, we ask for a contact name, email address, mailing address and method of payment. This information is used to set up your access to our service and for billing purposes. If we have a problem processing an order or receiving payment, the information is used to contact your business. We use this information to contact our customers, generally through email, to provide service updates, reminders and usage tracking information. To help us provide more targeted services through our web site(s), we also ask for some demographic information about the shop (such as number of technicians, services performed, number of bays, etc.). Providing demographic information is optional.

### Cancellation and Refund Policy

Our product is a month-to-month, paid-in-advance, web-based product. Our product can be cancelled at any time and does not contain a contract. For this reason, we offer no refunds as a matter of policy; however, at our option and discretion, exceptions can be made under special circumstance. If a refund is approved, it will appear as a credit on the billing credit card. If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please contact us at 1-800-745-9649, option 4.

### Information Use

Identifix.com is an automated and guided interactive diagnostic solution that provides a directed and dynamic step-by-step diagnostic process based on user input. It automatically assembles all relevant supporting information (specifications, diagrams, test procedures, component locations, TSBs, Repair-Tracs) needed by the technician to complete a successful diagnosis and repair. The information we gather enables approved technicians to access our web site for repair assistance. A log of each visit to our web site is stored by the customer and can be used to review the diagnostic steps and dates of repair completed on each vehicle. We also use this information to analyze the use and benefits of each feature of our site and to help us make improvements.

### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies log files and third parties to create a profile of our users. A “profile” is information that we keep on individual businesses detailing their viewing preferences and habits. Consequently, collected information is tied to business information and to individual users to improve the content of the site for the user, to target training and to provide offers. We do not share user profiles with third parties but will share account status with our in-house sales reps.

### Cookie

A “cookie” is a piece of data that is stored on the user’s computer and is tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies as well as persistent cookies. Once you close the browser, the session cookie simply ends while persistent cookies will be saved by your browser for retaining information for the next time you visit. We also use session ID cookies to keep one user’s activity separate from another’s if more than one user at your business accesses our site at the same time.

### Log Files

Like most standard web site servers, we use log files. “Log files” include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP) referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends and administer the site, track users’ movements in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information. Log files also store the record of each users’ site visit and provide the data for reviewing individual vehicle history.

### Communications from the Site

  * **Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new members a “welcome” email to verify password and user name. Established members will occasionally receive information on usage trends, site features, Identifix services, special offers and newsletters.
  * **Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions, it may be necessary to send users a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send our customers an email. These communications are not promotional in nature.
  * **Customer Service**  
We communicate with our customers on a regular basis to provide requested services. For issues concerning customer accounts, we reply via email or phone, depending on the customer’s preference.

### Sharing

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve our customers’ privacy, we may need to disclose user profile information if required by law, or if we have good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our web site.

### These are the instances in which we will share business information:

  * **Sales and Training Activities**  
Our in-house sales reps are told which repair facilities use identifix.com. We may also share customer usage information with them to assist site training activities for the specific customer, if needed.
  * **Business Transitions**  
In the event that Identifix is acquired by, or becomes part of, another company through sale or merger, our customers’ profile information will, in most instances, be considered part of these business transactions. If any such transactions occur, our customers will be notified in advance.
  * **Surveys and Contests**  
From time to time, our site requests information from users in the form of surveys or contests. Typically, this includes contact information such as what percentage of import vehicles represents the total vehicles you service. This information will help us monitor and improve our site. We will not share specific business information with third parties without prior approval from our customers. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary.
  * **Tell-A-Friend**  
If you send us the name and email address of a friend you think would like our site, we will send your friend a one-time email invitation to visit our site. Your name will appear on the email invitation as the person who sent us this reference. Identifix uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this email and tracking the success of our referral program.

### Security

Identifix has made a commitment to customer privacy, and we take every precaution to protect user information. Any sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or check routing number) that you submit is protected both online and offline. When you are asked to enter sensitive information, that information is stored in a separate system with no accessibility to the Internet.

Access to all sensitive customer information is restricted. Only employees whose job requires that they access this information (such as our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to sensitive information. In addition, these employees must use passwords to access our systems, and records are kept of their activities while they are accessing our systems. They log off the system whenever they leave their work areas.

All employees are kept up to date on our security and privacy practices and are instructed on an ongoing basis of any new security and privacy practices. If an employee leaves Identifix, their password and access to our systems are terminated. **If you have any questions about the security at identifix.com, please use our Contact Us page.**

### Supplementation of Information

To better serve our customers, we supplement the information we receive from our customers with demographic information from third-party sources. This may include industry association affiliations, sales, number of associates and business orientation.

### Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information

If you change your email, postal address, area code or phone number, or if you choose to discontinue using our service, please contact us at 651-633-8007, 7am-7pm Central Time, Monday-Friday, or use our Contact Us page.

### Notification of Changes

If we change our privacy policy in any way, we will post changes to this privacy statement to our home page and to other places we feel are appropriate so that our customers are always aware of the kind of information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we decide to use a customer’s business information in a manner different from what was stated in our privacy statement at the time they started using our service, we will notify them by email of this change. Customers will have a choice regarding whether or not we may use their information in this different manner.

Customers who have deleted or deactivated their Identifix account will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. Also, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect the customer information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site, notifying of the change. In some cases, in addition to posting a notice, we will also email customers that have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
